Finding Aid for the Sam Fleming Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- 28 Official Documents signed by Tennessee Governors, 1808-1930
  - Name index and folder number: (Box 6)
    Brownlow, William G., folder 10
    Buchanan, John P., folder 17
    Campbell, William B., folder 9
    Cannon, Newton, folder 5
    Carroll, William, folder 4
    Cox, John I., folder 22
    Frazier, James B., folder 21
    Hawkins, Alvin, folder 15
    Hooper, Ben W., folder 24
    Horton, Henry H., folder 27
    Jones, James C., folder 6
    Marks, Albert S., folder 14
    McMillan, Benton, folder 20
    McMinn, Joseph, folder 3
    Patterson, Malcolm R., folder 23
    Porter, James D., folder 13
    Roberts, A. H., folder 26.
    Rye, Tom C., folder 25
    Senter, DeWitt Clinton, folder 11
    Sevier, John, folder 1
    Taylor, Robert Love, folder 19
    Trousdale, William, folder 8
    Turney, Peter, folder 18
- Three prints (woodcuts of VU subjects signed by the Artists)
  - Old Gym (Box 7)
  - Kirkland Hall (Box 7)
  - Statue of Cornelius Vanderbilt (Box 7)